ISAÍ ARELLANO

Software Developer

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Guadalajara México

PHONE

3326673687

EMAIL

isai.arellano@outlook.com

SKILLS

Android Development
Android Studio
Java
Kotlin
iOS Development
Swift
Xcode
Flutter
Firebase
JavaScript
Angular
Svelte
Nodejs
MySQL
SOL-Server

PROFILE

Hello my name is Isaí, I consider myself a proactive person I always like to be learning and research on new technologies to keep up, I like to be self-taught and the state in different projects using different technologies, worked in a team without problems.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Software Developer - Mobile, TUIDENTIDAD

Guadalajara Jalisco

Mar 2020 — Present

In this position I work as a developer of native mobile applications, I have been in different areas, I have developed different android modules that we use so that our clients can consume our identity validation services through our SDKs (INE, ADDRESS-CFE), I have published the private SDKs through azure artifacts, I have been giving support to clients when they detect bugs, in the development I have used different tools to satisfy the needs such as http requests for the consumption of services, image management for sending to validation services of internal identity of the company, management of repositories through git, I have also participated in the development of internal services for identity validation with technologies such as Nodejs and Angular clients, always using good practices and delivering quality products

Software Engineer, CONTPAQi

Guadalajara Jalisco

Sep 2019 — Nov 2019

In this position initially I entered as a mobile application developer in which I was setting up their applications and solving a problem they had with their push notifications, at the same time I had to receive another application that was being made through an external provider in which I I was working in the part of organizing their tasks and making servers available so that they could mount their infrastructure, I also had the opportunity to participate in the internal systems area, I was making some improvements in the REST API using the programming languages

Web Programmer and Support, IBM

Guadalajara Jalisco

Jun 2018 — Aug 2019

In this position I was initially as a support for Heineken Mexico system, in which they sent us tickets through a ticketer, we assigned and resolved them depending on the priority, then, but at the same time I made supports they assigned me to do improvements in the system in which I used C # as backend and ASP.Net in the frontend, we used the SQL Server database and stored procedures for data access, here I made

LANGUAGES

English

Español

new functionalities in existing modules through method creation and modification of existing stored procedures

Android Mobile Application Developer, Ingeniería Aplicada T.I

Tequila Jalisco

Jan 2017 — Jun 2017

In this position I worked as a freelance developer for the development of an Android mobile application, with which my goal was to comply with the project of my residence and in which I used Java as the main language since it was for Native Android as well as the basis of SQL Server data accessing the data through REST API programmed in C # using HTTP methods sending parameters for its consumption, use GitLab as a versioner to take control of my development and the Google Maps API for the use of geolocation within the application

Web Developer, Ingeniería Aplicada T.I

Tequila Jalisco

Aug 2016 — Dec 2016

In this position I worked as a WEB Developer for a Government Accounting System, in which we used as C # backend and SQL SERVER databases, in my participation I had to perform stored procedures a, b, c, creation of classes for access to data through stored procedures, design and code interfaces using bootstrap framework components as well as some 3rd Party (DevExpress), I related in its 4 layers, I participated with 3 teammates with whom I exchanged my contributions through a versioner (SVN Subversion) and managed the activities that corresponded to me through an online project manager.

EDUCATION

Computer Engineering

Tequila Jalisco

2012 - 2016

IT Technician

Tequila Jalisco

2009 - 2012

COURSES

JAVA SE 6 Programmer, Oracle

Jan 2014 — Apr 2014

Cloud computing, Google

Jan 2020 — Feb 2020

REFERENCES

Pablo Riedel

CONTPAQi

33 1466 9611

Jose Luis Lerma

IBM

33 3455 9300